Guide to the Howard Zinn Papers TAM.542
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Series VIII: Subject Files, 1933-2010
  - Civil Disobedience: Plowshares Movement - AVCO Plowshares 7, 1983-1985 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Civil Disobedience: Plowshares Movement - Griffiss Plowshares 7, 1984-1985 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Civil Disobedience: Plowshares Movement - Plowshares 4, 1982-1983 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Civil Disobedience: Plowshares Movement - Plowshares 8, 1981-1990 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Civil Disobedience: Plowshares Movement - Plowshares 8 Resentencing Transcript, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Civil Disobedience: Plowshares Movement - Trident II Pruning Hooks, 1984-1986 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Civil Disobedience: Plowshares Movement - Various Actions, 1984-1985, 1997-1999 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Civil Disobedience: Walzer (Michael) Essay, 1968-1969, undated (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Civil Liberties, 1989-1991 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Civil Liberties, 1995-1999 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Civil Liberties, 2000-2001 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Civil Liberties, 2002 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Civil Liberties, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Civil Liberties, 2004 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Civil Liberties, 2005 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Civil Liberties, 2006 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Civil Liberties, Jan 2007-May 2007 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Civil Liberties, Jun 2007-Dec 2007 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Civil Liberties, 2008, undated (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Civil Liberties: Academic Freedom, 1949-1967 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Civil Liberties: Academic Freedom, 1970-1987, undated (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Civil Liberties: Academic Freedom - Kraus, Arthur J. Case, 1958, 1967-1972 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Civil Liberties: Bari, Judy and Darryl Cherney Case, 2001-2002 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Civil Liberties: Fifth Amendment, 1953-1956 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Civil Liberties: First Amendment - Falk, Richard Case and Earl Caldwell Case, 1970, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Civil Liberties: Free Speech from 1798-1917 (notes and fragments), undated (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Civil Liberties: Free Speech - Law, 1975-2002, undated (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Civil Liberties: Free Speech Lecture, 1975-1987, undated (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Civil Liberties: Free Speech - National Security, 1969-1989, undated (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Civil Liberties: Guantanamo, Torture, Media, 2008 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Civil Liberties: "Homefront Confidential" White Paper by the Reporters Committee for Freedom of the Press, 2002 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Civil Liberties: International, 1959-1969 (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Civil Liberties: International, 1971-1974 (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Civil Liberties: International, 1975 (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - Civil Liberties: International, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Civil Liberties: International, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Civil Liberties: International, 1978-1980, undated (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Civil Liberties: Speech - Extralegal, 1963-1976, 1989, undated (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Civil War (articles), 2008-2009 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Clippings: Various, 1961-1989 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Clippings: Various, 1990-2001 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Clippings: Various, 2001-2009, undated (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Columbus, Christopher: "Celebrate Columbus" - James Victore Poster, 1992, 2007 (Flat-file 1, Drawer 2)
  - Columbus, Christopher: "The Christopher Columbus Follies, an Eco-Cabaret", 1992 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Columbus, Christopher: Columbus, Indians and Expansion, 1991-1993, undated (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Columbus, Christopher: Columbus, the Indians and Human Progress (German translation of section from A People's History of the United States), [1992] (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Columbus, Christopher: "Constructing and Deconstructing the Historical Myths of Columbus..." by Donald A. Grinde, Jr., [1993] (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Columbus, Christopher: Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Columbus, Christopher: Notes, Articles, 1989-1992, undated (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Columbus, Christopher: Notes, Drafts and Fragments, undated (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Columbus, Christopher: Quincentennial, 1990-1992, undated (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Columbus, Christopher: Quincentennial Protests, 1991-1992 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Columbus, Christopher: Quincentennial Protests - Early Protest at Florida Museum of Natural History, 1989-1990 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Columbus, Christopher: Resources, 1989-1998, undated (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Columbus, Christopher: Rethinking Columbus, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Columbus, Christopher: Zinn Writings, 1991-1992, undated (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Communism (clippings), 1990 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Crime and Punishment, 1969-1986 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Crime and Punishment, 1991-2000 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Crime and Punishment, 2001-2008 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Crime and Punishment, undated (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Crime and Punishment: Abu-Jamal, Mumia, 1995-2000, undated (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Crime and Punishment: Capital Punishment, 1973-1999 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Crime and Punishment: Capital Punishment (includes letter from Russ Feingold), 2000-2009, undated (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Crime and Punishment: Capital Punishment - ...Last Meal by Jacquelyn C. Black, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Crime and Punishment: Capital Punishment - Zinn Writing and Notes, undated (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Crime and Punishment: "Class and the Economics of Crime" by David M. Gordon (two versions), 1971 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Crime and Punishment: Crime and Social Justice, A Journal of Radical Criminology, Spring-Summer 1974 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Crime and Punishment: Municipal Court - General, 1971-1973, undated (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Crime and Punishment: Municipal Court - "Melodrama in Dorchester in Five Acts," Student Paper by Julie Ann Hankin, 1972-1973 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Cuba, 1978, 1994, 2000-2004, undated (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Cuba: Missile Crisis, 1960-1963, 1998, undated (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Cuba: Vocabulary, 2004, undated (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Dioxin Poisoning (Agent Orange), 1978-1984, undated (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - "Domestic Ironies", 1999-2004, undated (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Draft Resistance, 1966-1972, undated (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Draft Resistance, 1980-1984, undated (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Drinnon, Richard, 1986 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - East Asia: Cambodia, 1958-1959 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - East Asia: China - Border Regions (includes Owen Lattimore materials), 1957-1966, undated (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - East Asia: China - Chiang Kai-shek, 1947-1962, undated (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - East Asia: China - Chinese Language, 1943-1961, undated (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - East Asia: China - Chinese Thought (religion and philosophy), 1958-1960, undated (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - East Asia: China - Civil Liberties, 1957-1960, undated (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - East Asia: China - Confucian Economy, undated (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - East Asia: China - Confucian Thought, undated (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - East Asia: China - Course on Chinese History (1800-1921), 1961-1962, undated (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - East Asia: China - Course on Contemporary China, 1960-1962, undated (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - East Asia: China - Economic and Social Change in Communist China, 1960-1961, undated (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - East Asia: China - Economy, 1960-1961, undated (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - East Asia: China - Fairbank, John K., The U.S. and China (Zinn notes), 1961, undated (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - East Asia: China - Family in China, 1960, undated (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - East Asia: China - "Freedom in Communist China" (selected translations from People's Daily), Aug 1961-Sep 1961 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - East Asia: China - General, 1947-1961, undated (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - East Asia: China - Geography, 1961, undated (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - East Asia: China - Government, Law and the Party, 1959-1962, undated (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - East Asia: China - History, 1961-1962, undated (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - East Asia: China - History (early), undated (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - East Asia: China - History, Modern China (1921-1960), 1961, undated (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - East Asia: China - Ideology, 1960-1964, undated (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - East Asia: China - Internal Conditions, 1956-1966, undated (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - East Asia: China - Kuo, Ping-Chia, China: New Age and New Outlook (Zinn notes), undated (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - East Asia: China - Lifton, Robert Jay, Thought Reform and the Psychology of Totalism (Zinn notes), undated (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - East Asia: China - Literature, 1960-1961, undated (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - East Asia: China - Mandarin Conversation, 1961-1962, undated (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - East Asia: China - Nationalities, 1961, undated (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - East Asia: China - Needham, Joseph (Zinn notes), undated (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - East Asia: China - Reform and Revolution - Sun Yat-Sen, John R. Fairbank and Joseph R. Levinson (Zinn notes), undated (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - East Asia: China - Relationship to the West, 1961, undated (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - East Asia: China - Rise of the Chinese Communist Party, undated (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - East Asia: China - Rostow, Walt, George Cressey and Richard Walker (Zinn notes), undated (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - East Asia: China - Sino-Indian Border War, 1962-1963, undated (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - East Asia: China - Taoism, undated (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - East Asia: China - US Foreign Policy toward China, 1958-1962, undated (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - East Asia: China - US Foreign Policy toward China, 1960-1966, undated (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - East Asia: China - Visitors, 1961-1962, undated (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - East Asia: China - Zinn Book Proposal ( China: The Shock of Recognition), 1961 (Box 47, Folder 32)
  - East Asia: China - Zinn Course "China: Past and Present", Spring 1962 (Box 47, Folder 33)
  - East Asia: China and America - Perceptions, 1961, undated (Box 47, Folder 34)
  - East Asia: China and Japan - History of East Asian Civilization ("Rice Paddies"), 1960-1961 (Box 47, Folder 35)
  - East Asia: China and Japan - Pelzel, John C., Values and Social Structure (Zinn notes), [1961] (Box 47, Folder 36)
  - East Asia: General - East and West, Race, 1944-1962, undated (Box 47, Folder 37)
  - East Asia: General - History, 1940s-1950s (Box 47, Folder 38)
  - East Asia: General - Survey, East Asian Civilization, circa 1960-1961 (Box 47, Folder 39)
  - East Asia: General - Wittfogel, Karl A., Oriental Despotism (Zinn notes), undated (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - East Asia: Indonesia, 1949-1957, undated (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - East Asia: Japan - History, 1965-1979, undated (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - East Asia: Japan - Student Movement (Includes "AMPO: A Report from the Japanese New Left"), 1969-1970, undated (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - East Asia: Korea, 1946-1967, undated (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - East Asia: Taiwan (Formosa), 1953-1961, undated (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - East Asia: Thailand, 1954-1956 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - East Asia: Transparencies - China Geography, Economy, Culture (I), undated (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - East Aisa: Transparencies - China Geography, Economy, Culture (II), undated (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - East Asia: Transparencies - China History (I), undated (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - East Asia: Transparencies - China History (II), undated (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - East Asia: Transparencies - Chinese Art, Religion, Cities, Maps (I), undated (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - East Asia: Transparencies - Chinese Art, Religion, Cities, Maps (II), undated (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - East Asia: Transparencies - Japan, USSR, undated (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Economics, 1966-1967 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Economics, 1973-1979 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Economics, 1980-Mar 1981 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Economics, Apr 1981-Jan 1982 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Economics, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Economics, 1983-1986 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Economics, 2007-2009 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Economics: Economic Facts, 1974-May 1975 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Economics: Economic Facts, Jun 1975-1976, undated (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Economics: Economic Facts, undated (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Economics: Economic Justice, 1974, 1985, 1991-2001, undated (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Economics: Economic Statistics, 1975-1980, undated (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Economics: Economics and Intervention, 1976-1985, undated (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Economics: Food, 1971-1976 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Economics: General, 1994-2009, undated (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Economics: Health and Safety, 1975-1979 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Economics: Health and Safety, 1980-1983, 1990-2009, undated (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Economics: History, 2002, undated (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Economics: Massachusetts Budget 1975, Sep 1975-Oct 1975, undated (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Economics: Massachusetts Welfare Crisis, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Economics: Oil and Energy, 1974-1978 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Economics: Oil and Energy, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Economics: Oil and Energy, 1980-1983 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Economics: Oil and Energy - Oil, Basic Information, undated (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Economics: Publications - "An Inquiry into the Nature and Causes of Inequities in the System of Taxation..." (Massachusetts Public Finance Project), 1973 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Economics: Publications - The Review of Radical Political Economics Vol. 7 No. 4, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Economics: Publications - Should a City Own a Bank? by Peter Anderson and Carl Kalvelage, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - Economics: Publications - What's Happening to Our Jobs? (Popular Economics Press), 1976 (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - Economics: Publications - Who Really Rules America? by Richard Pelton, 1970 (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Economics: Publications - Why Do We Spend So Much Money? (Popular Economics Press), 1975 (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Economics: Taxes, 1975-1977, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Economics: Utilities, 1973-1976, undated (Box 49, Folder 27)
  - Edelman, Marion Wright, 2009 (Box 49, Folder 28)
  - Ellison, Ella (Zinn article and related material on miscarriage of justice), 1974 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Ellsberg, Daniel, 1978-1988, undated (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Engels, Frederick: The Origin of the Family, Private Property and the State (Zinn notes), 1942, undated (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Environment: General, 1975-1978, undated (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Environment: General, 1981, 1983-1988, undated (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Environment: General, 1989-1991, undated (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Environment: General, 1992-1997, undated (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Environment: General, 2002-2004 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Environment: Nuclear Issues, 1964, 1970-1976 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Environment: Nuclear Issues, 1977-1978 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Environment: Nuclear Issues, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Environment: Nuclear Issues, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Environment: Nuclear Issues, 1981-2002 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Environment: Nuclear Issues, undated (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Environment: Nuclear Issues - Information Deception, 1974-1979, 1986-1988 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Environment: Nuclear Issues - Lovejoy, Sam, 1974, undated (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Environment: Nuclear Issues - Nader's Nuclear Issues by Dr. Ralph E. Lapp, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Environment: Nuclear Issues - "Report of the International Solidarity Conference for Survival" (Osaka, Japan), 1978 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Environment: Nuclear Issues - Seabrook Occupation, 1977 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Environment: Nuclear Issues - Silkwood, Karen, 1978, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - "Ethics and Politics, Behavior", 1953, 1966, undated (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - "Ethics and Politics, Behavior", 1961, 1966, undated (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - "The Family", 1973-1976, undated (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - "Famous Faces - From Nixon to Mao" (transparencies), undated (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI), 1972, 1989, undated (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - Federal Bureau of Investigation Informant Program: [Deposition] of John C. Ryan, 2001 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Films, undated (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Fiore, Patrick: "A People's History..." Images (paintings), 2007 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Foreign Policy, 1954-1990 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Foreign Policy, 1991-1999 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Foreign Policy, 2000-2003 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Foreign Policy, 2004-2009 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Foreign Policy, undated (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Foreign Policy: Clinton, 1993-1999, undated (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Foreign Policy: Ethics, undated (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Foreign Policy: Grenada, undated (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Foreign Policy: Public Opinion, 1981-1989, undated (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Foreign Policy: Roosevelt, Franklin D., undated (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Foreign Policy: Roosevelt, Theodore and Taft, undated (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Freedom of Information Act (FOIA), 1966-1988 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Freedom of Information Act (FOIA): Correspondence, 1975-1980 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Freedom of Information Act (FOIA): Government Secrecy (includes court documents from James Lafferty, et al. v. William Rogers, et al.), 1970-1975, undated (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Gender and Security Issues, 2009 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Globalization, 2000-2002 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Goldberg, Harvey, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Goldman, Emma: [Article] Draft, undated (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Gulf Wars: 1990-1991, First Gulf War - Before Beginning of Aerial Bombardment, Aug 1990-Mar 1991 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Gulf Wars: 1990-1991, First Gulf War - Bush Arguments for War (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Gulf Wars: 1990-1991, First Gulf War - Casualties (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - Gulf Wars: 1990-1991, First Gulf War - "Hypocrisy", 1990-1992 (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - Gulf Wars: 1990-1991, First Gulf War - Opinions (Box 51, Folder 26)
  - Gulf Wars: 1990-1991, First Gulf War - Overview, 1991-1998, undated (Box 51, Folder 27)
  - Gulf Wars: 1990-1991, First Gulf War - The Press (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - Gulf Wars: 1990-1991, First Gulf War - Protests (Box 51, Folder 29)
  - Gulf Wars: 1990-1991, First Gulf War - Protests, 1991-1992, undated (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Gulf Wars: 1990-1991, First Gulf War - Zinn Articles, Drafts, Notes, 1991, undated (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Gulf Wars: 1998, Iraq Crisis, 1990-1994, 1997-1998, undated (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Gulf Wars: 1998, Iraq Crisis, 1998-2000, undated (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Gulf Wars: 1998, Iraq Crisis - Correspondence between Zinn and Barney Frank (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Gulf Wars: 2001-, Afghanistan and Iraq - Afghanistan, 2001-2008, undated (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Gulf Wars: 2001-, Afghanistan and Iraq - Afghanistan, Casualties, Oct 2001-Nov 2001 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Gulf Wars: 2001-, Afghanistan and Iraq - Afghanistan, Casualties, Dec 2001-2003, undated (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Gulf Wars: 2001-, Afghanistan and Iraq - Anti-war Resistance / Actions, 2002-2003 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Gulf Wars: 2001-, Afghanistan and Iraq - Anti-war Resistance / Actions, 2004-2005 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Gulf Wars: 2001-, Afghanistan and Iraq - Bombing, Casualties, 2003, undated (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Gulf Wars: 2001-, Afghanistan and Iraq - Hypocrisy, 2003-2004, undated (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Gulf Wars: 2001-, Afghanistan and Iraq - Iraq, 2002-2008, undated (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Gulf Wars: 2001-, Afghanistan and Iraq - Iraq, Anti-War Opinion, 2003-2004 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Gulf Wars: 2001-, Afghanistan and Iraq - Iraq, Casualties, 2003-2006, undated (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Gulf Wars: 2001-, Afghanistan and Iraq - Iraq, U.S. Handover, 2004-2005, undated (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Gulf Wars: 2001-, Afghanistan and Iraq - Lies, 2002-2003, undated (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Gulf Wars: 2001-, Afghanistan and Iraq - Occupation, 2002-2003 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Gulf Wars: 2001-, Afghanistan and Iraq - Occupation, 2004-2005, undated (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Gulf Wars: 2001-, Afghanistan and Iraq - Torture, 2004-2005, undated (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Gulf Wars: 2001-, Afghanistan and Iraq - U.S.-Iraq History, 1999, 2002-2008, undated (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Gulf Wars: Guantanamo, 2004-2009, undated (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Gulf Wars: Iraq, 1990-2000, undated (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Gulf Wars: "A Threat to Peace" (poster), [2002] (Flat-file 1, Drawer 2)
  - Haiti, undated (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Hawaii, undated (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Health Issues, 1968-2007, undated (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Health Issues: "Consumer Interest and Health Reform: The Logic of Withdrawal from Managed Competition" Presentation by Gordon D. Schiff, M.D., 1994 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Helms, Richard: Perjury Case, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Hicks, Kevin: Writings, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Hicks, Kevin: Writings, 1998 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Hicks, Kevin: Writings - "Chained and Unchained", 2006-2007 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Hicks, Kevin: Writings - "Kevin, Monkey Monk and the Atomic Funk", 2006 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Hicks, Kevin: Writings - "The Phoenix", 1996 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Hicks, Kevin: Writings - Rebel Angel or The Confessions of an Angry Nigger!, 1992 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Hicks, Kevin: Writings - "Valley of the Shadows or Diary of Darkness", 1993 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - History, 1954, 1965-1981 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - History, 1969-1994 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - History, 1985-1997 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - History, 1995-2006, undated (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - History, 1998-2003 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - History, 2003-2007 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - History (I), undated (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - History (II), undated (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - History: Alien and Sedition Act (1798), 1967, undated (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - History: American Revolution, 1979, 1992, 2004, undated (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - History: Archives, "Oral History of the American Left" (newsletter), 1979-1980, undated (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - History: Class Conflict - 19th Century, 1979, 1988, undated (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - History: Essays (by Zinn and others), 1975-1982, undated (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - History: Haymarket Riots, 1986, undated (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - History: Manifest Destiny, 1941-2004, undated (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - History: Mexican War, 1979 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - History: The New Deal, 1967-1993, undated (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - History: Notes, 1967-1973, undated (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - History: Philosophy of History, 1988, undated (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - History: Potency, 1975-1979, undated (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - History: Science and History, 1967-1982, undated (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - History: The Sixties, 1979, 1997, 1999, undated (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - History: The Sixties, undated (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - History: Socialist Movements of the Early 20th Century, 1968, 1979-1989, undated (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - History: Truman Administration, 1955-1956, 1964, 1974, undated (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - History: U.S. Bibliography, 1970-1978 (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - History: U.S. Bibliography, 1975-1978, undated (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - History: U.S. Diplomatic History, 1959, undated (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - History: U.S. History (class), 1956-2001, undated (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - History: U.S. and Latin America, 1979-1986, 2003, undated (Box 54, Folder 23)
  - History: Wilson, Woodrow - Foreign Policy Pre-WWI, undated (Box 54, Folder 24)
  - History: Works Progress Administration (WPA), 1937, 1978, 1995, undated (Box 54, Folder 25)
  - History: World History, undated (Box 54, Folder 26)
  - History: World War I, 1939, 1972, undated (Box 54, Folder 27)
  - History: World War II, 1945-1955, undated (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - History and Science: Objectivity, 1965-1992, undated (Box 54, Folder 29)
  - The Holocaust, 1979-1989, 2003, undated (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - The Holocaust: Notes on Peter Novick's The Holocaust in American Life (1999), undated (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Hope, 1990s (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Hope, 2000 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Hope, 2001 (Box 55, Folder 5)